Start on the exact operational screen for this guide.
Open Booking Detail before approving a customer package.
Review submitted agreement and insurance signals before approval.
Verify identity, license, contact, vehicle, dates, and insurance against the booking.
Open approval only after operational blockers are clear.
Do not approve if identity, agreement, insurance, vehicle availability, amount, or deposit risk is unclear.
Open Review & approve after checking the submitted customer package.
Set high-risk and deposit only when the customer package supports the decision.
Approve and notify customer. This unlocks payment; it does not mark the booking paid.
After approval, copy the payment link only after confirming the customer and booking code.