The confirmation link opens the customer verification wizard for this booking code.
Start with the rental summary and continue only if the booking code, dates, vehicle, and total look right.
The customer scans the license barcode when possible, or uses manual entry if camera scan is unavailable.
Manual entry is the fallback when scanning is not available.
Enter the legal street address.
Enter city.
Select the customer state.
Enter date of birth for verification.
Continue after address and date of birth are complete.
Enter the driver license number.
Select the issuing state.
Enter license expiration.
License photos are optional, but they speed up admin verification and pickup.
Continue after license fields are complete.
Open and read the full terms before accepting.
Accept terms only after scrolling to the end.
Continue after terms are accepted.
Every acknowledgement must be checked before the signature step.
Continue after all acknowledgements are checked.
Typed signature is available when drawing is not ideal.
Type the customer legal signature.
Continue to insurance after signature is saved.
Choose personal insurance or Bonzah coverage before review.
Enter insurance company.
Enter policy number.
Enter policy expiration.
Continue to review; payment is still gated by approval.
Review the itemized package before submitting for approval.
Submit the completed package for admin approval.
The customer waits here until admin approval unlocks payment.